<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Caffeinspiration</title>
    <link>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Caffeinspiration</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Your Personal Blog on GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/default/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/default/</guid>
      <description>Content for your bog post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/3-first-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/3-first-night/</guid>
      <description>We only stopped a minute in our appartment before heading back out to eat.
What an experience, to be exhausted from our travel, on the other side of the planet, in an entirely new country, and walking down a busy student / foreigner bar streets.
Closest picture I could find, though not as busy and not as late
···
Hongdae Street, credit Thorsten Ueberschaer on Google Maps, I was too tired / amazed / hungry to bother taking a picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/4-tteokbokki/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/4-tteokbokki/</guid>
      <description>Lunch!
After a long, restful night, we are ready for some excitement. Let&amp;rsquo;s skip the bibimbap for now (rice and vegetables&amp;hellip; boooriiing) and go straight to the good stuff, TTeokbokki.
The quintissential Korean street food, it has been a stable of JJ and me&amp;rsquo;s pre-trip youtube hype sessions. It&amp;rsquo;s a relatively simple dish, consisting of rice cake noodles (thick, unflavoured cylinders of rice flour dough) simmered in traditional Korean chili paste, gochujang, possibly sometimes with hints of fish cake broth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/5-chips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/5-chips/</guid>
      <description>Convenience store run! Undeterred by our lunch let&amp;rsquo;s get some crazy foreign chip flavours, and some familiar ones.
[pic]
Omg, these all taste super sweet. Is this going to be a running theme with the food here?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/6-covid-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zacharyvernec.github.io/posts/6-covid-test/</guid>
      <description>One of the entry requirements to South Korea is to take a PCR test within 1 calendar day of our plane landing. Most people choose to take the test at the airport&amp;rsquo;s clinic, but due to our plane delay we had already missed our appointment on landing. We took the opportunity to rest.
Keep in mind, at this point I was not seriously believing I had covid. Yes, I was sick on the plane, but I had just gotten my booster shot earlier in the week?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
